Preliminary Guide to the John C. Lilly papers M0786
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 9. Reprints, by author [M-Z incomplete]
  - Pilleri G. and R.G. Busnel (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Olsen, C. Robert et al (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Payne, Roger and Douglas Webb (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Pryor, Karen W. (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Pepper, Ross L. and J.V. Simmons, Jr. (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Pepper Ross I. and J.V. Simmons Jr. (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Petelina, E.V. (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Pilleri, Georg and Carola Kraus (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Pilleri, G. (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Purves, P.E. and Utrecht, Van (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Pilleri, G. (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Purves, P.E. (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Osen, KK., Jansen J. (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - Poulter, T.C. (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - Ridgway S.H., McCormick J.G. and Wever E.G. (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - Ridgway S. and Bullock T.H. (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - Ridgway S.H. and B.L. Scronce (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - Keysenbach de Haan, F.W. (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Schevill, William E., et al (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Spong, Paul and Don White (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Schusterman, Ronald J. (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Schmalbruch, H. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Saayman G.S., C.K. Tayler, D. Bower (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Schevill W.E. and W.A. Watkins (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Shurepova, G.A. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Zlatoustova L.V. and A.B. Nizova (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Sommer, C.S. (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Tsikora, S. (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Snong, Paul and Don White (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Sokolov, V. (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Tower D.B. and O.M. Young (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Thompson, R.K.R., Herman L.M. (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Taylor, C.K. and G.S. Saayman (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Sales, Gillian and Pye, David (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Turner, R.N. (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Schevill, W.E. (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Sukhoruchenko, M.N. (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Sukhovskaya, L.I. (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Sukhouskaya, C.I. (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Saprykin, V.A. (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Steinberg, J.C. (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Tomlin, A.G. (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Taylor, C.K. (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Saayman, G.S. (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Viamonke M. et al (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Verbitskaia, L.B. (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Varanasi, Usha (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Voronin L.G. et al (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Voronin L.G. and L.B. Kozarovitskii (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Malins D.C. and Varanasi Usha (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Wood F.G. et al (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Wedmid, Yuri and Litchfield, Carter (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - White, Don et al (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Wever E.C., McCormick J.G. et al (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Wever, E.G., McCormick J.G. et al (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Wever, Ernest Glen et al (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Whitlow W.L. et al (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Watkins, William A (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - Verbitskaia, L.B. (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - Viamonte, M. (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - Whales Research Institute (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - Yunker M.P. and L.M. Herman (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - Yunker M.P. and L.M. Herman (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - Zaslavskii G.L. (Box 33, Folder 47)
  - Zvorykin, V.T. (Box 33, Folder 48)
  - Zvorykin, V.P. (Box 33, Folder 49)
- Series 10. Reprints [non-alphabetical]
  - Graven, Jacques (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Toles, George E. (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Wilson - Sociobiology (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Ray, Carleton (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Pryor, Karen W., R. Haag & J.O'Reilly (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Morgan, S. (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Kellogg, Winthrop N. (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Caldwell, D.K. & M.C. Caldwell (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Droscher, Vitus B. (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Breland, K. & M. Breland (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Marine Mammals - Success in the Sea (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Audrew, R.J. (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Tschernezky, W. (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Tavolga, M.C. (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Glass, B.P. (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Atz, J.W. (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Jones-Campbell, Simon (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Bibliography of Dolphins, Porpoises, Cetacea Notebooks (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Series 11. Photographs, slides, negatives
  Existence and Location of Copies
  Prints in Box 152 (accession 2015-06) have been scanned by the donor and are available digitally.
  - Atlantis Theatre at Sea World, photographs, circa 1976 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Collected works of John C. Lilly, microfiche, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Dolphin dissection, photograph (Flat-box 61, Folder 2)
  - Human/Dolphin Foundation, photographs of John Lilly and others (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Japan photographs, circa 1992 (Box 59, Folder 4-5)
  - Mind of the Dolphin/Man and Dolphin, photographs (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Mind of the Dolphin/Man and Dolphin, photographs (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - John Lilly, photo album (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Slides (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - U.S. Naval Missile Center, dolphin research photographs, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Dolphin research (13 lantern slides) (Flat-box 59A)
  - Prints and negatives- family, skiing, travel, 1936-1945 (Box 147)
    Negatives and selected prints in original labeled envelopes depicting the Lilly family in Hanover, Swarthmore, St. Paul, Pasadena and elsewhere, as well as on various trips. Many are of skiing.
  - 1 B&W negative roll labeled "All JCL?"; 1 roll Kodachrome 1954 (Box 145)
  - Negatives (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - Negs of Ski Trip (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Calif. CalTech Pre-Marriage B + W Fotos +2 B + W Negs (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Lilly 1 Big 1939 Skiing Neg (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - B + W Neg. of the Radio STA. St. Paul (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - Small B + W Neg. (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - JL JR. in Hanover? 1 W/ML - 2 Negs of same (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - 1933 Air Races Etc. B + W Fotos (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - 1938 Copies of Anatomy Photos + Text (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - B + W Fotos St. Paul 1930s JCL (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Misc. Not Photos, tickets, 3 B + W Negs (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Big B + W Negs of Skiing 1940 Lassen Many, Scenic Views (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 130, Folder 17)
  - Negatives (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Photographs (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Pasadena 1953 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Photographs (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Photograph and Clipping (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 131, Folder 12)
  - Carcajow Ski Club (Box 131, Folder 13)
  - John C. Lilly Photographs (Box 131, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 131, Folder 15)
  - Negatives (Box 131, Folder 17)
  - Pics of Pres + Hanging tree (Box 131, Folder 18)
  - Photo Negatives (Box 131, Folder 19)
  - Photo Negatives (Box 131, Folder 20)
  - Negatives (Box 131, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 131, Folder 22)
  - Various Photographs (Box 131, Folder 23)
  - [Qalesvile?] Negatives (Box 131, Folder 27)
  - John C. Lilly and Family Photographs (Box 131, Folder 28)
  - Sail Boat Pictures (Box 131, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 131, Folder 30)
  - Various Photographs and Negatives (Box 131, Folder 31)
  - Slides (Box 131, Folder 32)
  - Slides (Box 131, Folder 33)
  - Slides and Negatives (Box 131, Folder 34)
  - Various Photographs (Box 131, Folder 35)
  - Negatives (Box 133)
  - Negatives (Box 134)
  - Photographs by Sam Chambliss (Box 138, Folders 1-2)
  - Photograph by Fred Hess & Sons (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Photograph Christmas 1952 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Photograph by Everett Kroeger Neg. No. 0-336-E (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Photograph by Everett Kroeger (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Norman Viken '41 (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - 2015-096 Photograph inventory [also available digitally] (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - John C. Lilly Photo Series [54 copy prints], 1915-1950 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - John C. Lilly Family & Friends [copy prints] (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Lilly Dolphin House & Related Materials [copy prints] (Box 152, Folder 4)
    Lilly Dolphin Structure Images [11]; Lilly at Marineland, Coconut Grove Florida, and Janus Project, Redwood City, California [33]; Margaret Howe and Peter Dolphin Photo Series
  - John C. Lilly Portraits [copy prints] (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Lilly Book Cover Images [copy prints] (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - Lilly Mix Media Ephemera [copy prints] (Box 152, Folder 7)
- Series 12. Audiovisual media
  - 12.1 Audiotape reels (dolphin research)
    Preservation note:
    Audio has been digitally captured from reels in Box 79, 82, 99, 105, 106, 108 and 120.
    Cartons 67-115 contain audiotape reels with recordings of John C. Lilly’s dolphin experiments conducted between 1961-1968. The box-level listings include the names of the predominate dolphin test subjects, the rough date range of the recordings, and the extent and size of the reels in the box. Occasionally the listings contain additional information, such as the name of the experiment being performed or other details.
    The audiotape reel cases usually contain additional handwritten notes and commentary by Lilly regarding the contents of the recordings. Notes indicate the names of the test subjects, the activity being recorded, such as feeding sessions or the names of various experiments (i.e., vocal output; language; visual acoustics of sound production; repeated sounds; voice spectrum transfer; LSD; Ultrasonic analysis; telephone system; etc.), technical information about the recorded session, and more detailed information about the time, date, and duration of the recorded activity.
    The number of audiotape reels per carton is listed in parentheses, as well as the size of the reels. For example (10 audiotapes, 12"; 3 audiotapes, 7") indicates that the carton contains ten 12" inch audiotape reels and three 7" inch audiotape reels. The majority of reels in the collection are 7" or 12"; but there also some 3" and 5" reels.
    - Cheechee, Elvar, Sissy (38 audiotapes, 7"), 1962-07 (Box 145, Box 67)
    - Cheechee, Elvar, Sissy (38 audiotapes, 7"), 1962 June-July (Box 68)
    - Cheechee, Crane, Elvar, Sissy, Stenella (35 audiotapes, 7"), 1961-1962 (Box 69)
    - Cheechee, Elvar, Sissy (38 audiotapes, 7"), 1962 May-June (Box 70)
    - Cheechee, Elvar, Sissy (38 audiotapes, 7"), 1962 May-June (Box 71)
    - Cheechee, Elvar, Sissy (38 audiotapes, 7"), 1962 January-March (Box 72)
    - Cheechee, Elvar, Sissy (38 audiotapes, 7"), 1962 April-May (Box 73)
    - Cheechee, Elvar, Sissy (81 audiotapes, 3"), 1961-1962 (Box 74)
    - Cheechee, Elvar, Peanuts, Sissy (38 audiotapes, 7"), 1962-1965 (Box 75)
    - Baby, Cheechee, Sissy (38 audiotapes, 7"), 1963-1965 (Box 76)
    - Pam, Peter, Sissy (38 audiotapes, 7"), 1963 May-June (Box 77)
    - Cheechee, Elvar (39 audiotapes, 7"), 1964 May-August (Box 78)
    - Pam, Peter, Sissy (21 audiotapes, 7"), 1963 April (Box 79)
    - Baby, Cheechee, Elvar (38 audiotapes, 7"), 1964-1965 (Box 80)
    - Baby, Cheechee, Pam, Peter, Sissy (38 audiotapes, 7"), 1962-1965 (Box 81)
    - Pam, Peter, Sissy (38 audiotapes, 7"), 1963 April-November (Box 82)
    - Pam, Peter, Sissy (38 audiotapes, 7"), 1962-1964 (Box 83)
    - Baby (11 audiotapes, 12"; 2 audiotapes, 7"), 1965 June-February (Box 84)
    - Visual acoustics of sound production (12 audiotapes, 12"), 1965 May (Box 85)
    - Baby, Cheechee, Elvar, Jobe, Lady (12 audiotapes, 12"), 1965 February-May (Box 86)
    - Notch, Pequot (12 audiotapes, 12"), 1965 May-June (Box 87)
    - Baby, Notch, Pequot (12 audiotapes, 12") (Box 88)
    - Lady, Pequot (12 audiotapes, 12"; 1 audiotape, 7"), 1965-1967 (Box 89)
    - Speech perception, word repetition, Ladiat experiments (11 audiotapes, 12"; one empty case), 1968 (Box 90)
    - Ladiat experiments (12 audiotapes, 12"; 1 audiotape, 7"), 1968 June (Box 91)
    - Ladiat experiments (12 audiotapes, 12"), 1968 June (Box 92)
    - Baby, Cheechee, Lady, Pequot; Ladiat experiments (12 audiotapes, 12"), 1962-1968 (Box 93)
    - Cheechee, Elvar, Jobe, Peanut (12 audiotapes, 12"; 1 audiotape, 5"), 1964 April-September (Box 94)
    - Baby, Cheechee, Elvar, Grandma, Lady, Pequot, Typee (12 audiotapes, 12"), 1963-1964 (Box 95)
    - Cheechee, Cookie, Elvar, Grandma, Pequot, Typee (12 audiotapes, 12"; 1 audiotape, 7"), 1963 November (Box 96)
    - Baby, Cheechee, Elvar, Pequot; Ted Nelson observing (11 audiotapes, 12"), 1962-1963 (Box 143, Box 97)
    - Baby and Mother, Cheechee, Elvar, Sissy (12 audiotapes, 12"), 1962 August-September (Box 98)
    - Baby and Mother, Cheechee, Elvar, Sissy (12 audiotapes, 12"), 1962-1965 (Box 99)
    - Sissy and two bulls (12 audiotapes, 12"), 1962 August-September (Box 100)
    - Cheechee, Elvar, Sissy (12 audiotapes, 12"), 1961-1962 (Box 101)
    - Baby and Mother, Cheechee, Elvar, Sissy (12 audiotapes, 12"), 1962 July-August (Box 102)
    - Jobe, Lady, Notch, Pequot, Sissy (37 audiotapes, 7"; 3 audiotapes, 12"), 1962-1967 (Box 103)
    - Jobe, Lady, Notch, Pequot (46 audiotapes, 7"), 1966-1967 (Box 104)
    - Jobe, Lady, Notch, Pequot, Peter, Sissy (46 audiotapes, 7"), 1965-1966 (Box 105)
    - Peter, Sissy (40 audiotapes, 7"; 7 audiotapes, 5"), 1965-1966 (Box 106)
    - Pam, Peter, Sissy (46 audiotapes, 7"), 1965-1966 (Box 107)
    - Pam, Peter, Sissy, 1964-1966 (Box 108)
    - Cheechee, Elvar, Pequot (43 audiotapes, 7"; 1 audiotape, 5"), 1962-1964 (Box 109)
    - Cheechee, Elvar, Sissy (43 audiotapes, 7"; 1 audiotape, 5"), 1962-1964 (Box 110)
    - Cheechee, Elvar (42 audiotapes, 7"; 2 audiotapes, 5"), 1963-1964 (Box 111)
    - Cheechee, Cookie, Elvar, Pequot, Typee, Mother and Baby (45 audiotapes, 7"), 1963-1964 (Box 112)
    - Cheechee, Elvar, Pequot, Sissy (45 audiotapes, 7"), 1962-1964 (Box 113)
    - Cheechee, Elvar, Pequot (44 audiotapes, 7"; 1 audiotape, 5"), 1963-1964 (Box 114)
    - Cheechee, Elvar, Grandma, Pequot (22 audiotapes, 7"; 3 audiotapes, 5"), 1963-1964 (Box 115)
    - Cheechee, Elvar, Pequot, Sissy (46 audiotapes, 7"; 3 audiotapes, 5"), 1964-1965 (Box 120)
  - 12.2 Film and video
    - [R#4?] Kodak 16mm film (Box 145)
    - Lilly family films (3 16mm reels) (Box 137, Reels 1-3)
    - Lilly family films (DVD transfers) (Box 137, Videodisc 1-3)
    - Emerging Love Between Man and Dolphins (Box 122, Videotape 4)
    - Performance Tape - Short Versions of Simulations. Tahiti Slides (Wizard Poem Dyadic Mobilabile). Wedding Slides, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 145)
    - For John C. Lilly: With Love From Faustin & Brian & Creon, 1997; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 145)
    - John Lilly. Cetacean Nation. In Floating Chair with Virtual Room, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 145)
    - The Dolphin Touch [1], 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 144, Item 1)
      Transferred.
    - John Lilly ICC Speech [2], 1976-01-10; 2 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 144, Item 2-3)
    - Dolphins - Raw Footage "Breaking the Dolphin Code" William Rader [4], 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 144, Item 4)
    - Tomorrow Show & Tom Snyder, John & Toni Lilly [5], 1975-11-11; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 144, Item 5)
    - Today Show, John Lilly [6], 1979-02; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 144, Item 6)
    - John's Japanese interview - Sound Photosynthesis [7], 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 144, Item 7)
    - Visions of Today, Dolphin Panel, 1983-01-08; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic s) (Box 148, Item 1)
    - Digital Voice. Session #56, 1983-09-06; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 148, Item 2)
    - JANUS III Test, 1980-12; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 148, Item 3)
    - Altered States Reel #1 [cassette] / Third Day in Channel [case], 1981-01-28; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 148, Item 4)
    - JANUS 1, Joe & Rosalie Context Session #1, 1980-11; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 148, Item 5)
    - JANUS 1, 2, 3, 1981-01 (Box 148, Item 6)
    - JANUS 1, 3, 1980-12-06; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 149, Item 1)
    - Talkabout, Truman Jacques, John & Toni Lilly, 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 149, Item 2)
    - Declassified: Navy Dolphins. IBVA, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 149, Item 3)
    - [Japanese?], 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 149, Item 4)
    - JCL/ICERC/Hawaii, 1992; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 149, Item 5)
    - John Lilly NHK, 1992-11-18; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 149, Item 6)
    - Dr. John C. Lilly / Japanese TV Coverage I.C.E.R.C. Japan, 1992; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 149, Item 7)
    - Oil Fires of Kuwait June 91; Aspen Institute for Advanced Studues, Adam Trombley, Physicist (Box 153, Object 1)
    - Se Remettre Au Monda - Monica Peloquin. Emission: Science et Technologie, 1983-04-03 (Box 153, Object 2)
    - The December Wrap, From Co-Directions, Inc. (Box 153, Object 3)
    - The Hero's Journey. For John Lilly on his Birthday 1989 (Box 153, Object 4)
    - Performance. Mick Jagger. Campbell Dream (Box 153, Object 5)
    - Space Biospheres. World News Tonite (Box 153, Object 6)
    - Cinepro/CVI Brumbar. Pacific Shift Prod. Dub Raw Footage, 1985-10-13 (Box 153, Object 7)
    - Discas Voadores (TV Manchete Celoso) Thomaz, Na Fazenda Da Sonia. Programa 3a Visao Sobre UFOs (Box 153, Object 8)
    - Whales Alive Tape #5 (Box 153, Object 9)
    - Secret Government - Moyers; The Secret Team - Sheehan; Shadow Government - Avirgan; Peace in Guatemala (Box 153, Object 10)
    - Whales Alive (Special Conference. Tape #1 June 7th; Tape #3 June 10th & 11th. Boston Mass. Copy, 1983-06 (Box 153, Object 11)
    - Test Tape. 6hr Mode. JCL, Gina, Theresa, JCL, Bicycle, 1982-03-12 (Box 153, Object 12)
    - A Idade Da Terra (Box 153, Object 13)
    - Seafari Demo. Amos Nouchon (Box 154, Object 1)
    - Bali Documentary (Box 154, Object 2)
    - Brainstorm. Human/Dolphin Foundation (Box 154, Object 3)
    - Philosopher's Stone. For John From Faustin & Brian (Box 154, Object 4)
    - Whales Alive Tape #6 (Box 154, Object 5)
    - Orca The Killer Whale. Paramount, 1977 (Box 154, Object 6)
    - Get Me Down From Here (1989) From Rocktoons; Tutcha Rock (1990) From Rocktoons; The Shemutti Plain (1991) From Jazzrap [etc.] (Box 154, Object 7)
    - Nina's 40th Birthday Party, 1989-03-19 (Box 154, Object 8)
    - City in the Sky. A Virtual Gallery Exhibit Featuring the Works of E.J. Gold. Computer Animation by Tim Elston (Box 154, Object 9)
  - 12.3 Audio
    - Tank V. UFO audiocassettes
      - Tank: 601 (Box 135, Cassette 1)
      - "Tank-VS-UFO" (Box 135, Cassette 2)
      - P. 156 @ 53-67 Tank-V-UFO (Box 135, Cassette 3)
      - Tank-V- UFO: 605 (Box 135, Cassette 4)
      - T-V-U: 750-810 (Box 135, Cassette 5)
    - Hawaii's Humpbacks... their vocalizations (Box 135, Cassette 6)
    - John Lilly May 23, 1989 KBNO (AM + FM) Radio (Box 135, Cassette 7)
    - One (Box 135, Cassette 8)
    - 1992 Pecos Tape 4 (Box 135, Cassette 9)
    - 1. NBC 2. Interviews 3. Grad. 1961, 3 audiotape reel(s) (Box 136, Item 1)
    - Las Vegas Willard Ware interviewed by C. R. R. 1971, 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 136, Item 2)
    - Untitled Reel, 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 136, Item 3)
    - Untitled Reel, 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 136, Item 4)
    - Untitled Reel, 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 136, Item 5)
    - Untitled Reel, 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 137, Item 6)
    - Untitled Reel, 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 137, Item 7)
    - Sounds and the Ultra-Sounds of the Bottle-Nose Dolphin (Folkways FW06132), 1973; 1 audio disc(s) (Flat-box 146, Folder 2)
      LP produced and narrated by Lilly. Available here: http://www.folkways.si.edu/sounds-and-ultra-sounds-of-the-bottle-nose-dolphin/album/smithsonian
    - An interview with John C. Lilly, Toni Lilly, Joe Hart, 1973-09-30; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 149, Item 8)
      Come To Life: A Human Growth Center of the Air, Produced by Herschel Lymon for Pacifica Radio KPFK:FM
    - John Lilly Day CSUS Reading. Prologue in Simulations of God, 2 audiotape reel(s) (Box 149, Items 9-10)
    - Yellow Magic Orchestra ‎– Technodon (Eastworld TOCT-8010), 1993; 1 compact disc(s) (Box 149, Item 11)
    - John C Lilly ‎– E.C.C.O. (Hachiman ‎ IS93-0001), 1993; 1 compact disc(s) (Box 149, Item 12)
    - Sound Photosynthesis cassettes, 1978-1992; 14 audiocassette(s) (Box 150, Items 1-14)
    - John Pancho Eugenio, 1982-03-20 (Box 150, Item 15)
    - [answering machine cassette] (Box 150, Item 16)
    - Chap I. SOG (Box 150, Item 17)
    - John C. Lilly - Alternity & Future History (Sound Photosynthesis), 1989; 5 audiocassette(s) (Box 151, Item 1)
      Title taken from case. The 5 cassettes inside do not share that title and may not be original to the set. The back of the case does indicate "variety pack" however.
    - The English Journal 8, 1993-08 (Box 151, Item 2)
      Japanese audio magazine with Lilly feature "Through the Tank and LSD the Whole Universe Opened Up."
    - Lecture: Texas A&M University. Human Software, Inc., 1977-02-03 (Box 151, Item 3)
    - Lecture: Pomona College. Human Software, 1977-01-13 (Box 151, Item 4)
    - Lecture: California Celebrates the Whale. Human Software, Inc., 1976-11-20 (Box 151, Item 5)
  - 12.4 Numbered A/V and photographs #1-37
    - 1. Arthur C. Clarke "Message From The Future," with John C. Lilly, March 1993 [1 VHS, 2 DVD] (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - 2. John C. Lilly, 4th International Dolphin and Whale Conference, Japan 1994 [VHS] (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - 3. John C. Lilly, "The Grandfather of Communication," NTT Presents Dr John C. Lilly, July 19, 1994 [2 VHS] (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - 4. John C. Lilly Dolphin Research Documentary, "Emerging Love Between Man and Dolphin" [3 videocassettes, 1 DVD] (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - 5. John C. Lilly Interview, Maui Interview, Hi Quality Japanese Footage, 8-26, 1993 [1 Beta, 2 DVD] (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - 6. John C. Lilly in Blue Room Studio, New York City, Fall 1998, with BigTwin artist in residence and Lilly website designer [2 VHS, 2 DVD] (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - 7. Orphans of Time with John C. Lilly [1 VHS, 2 DVD] (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - 8. John C. Lilly on Maui Dolphin Cruises 1990's [1 VHS, 2 DVD] (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - 9. In the Wild, with Dr. John C. Lilly and Robin Williams, 1996, Tigress Productions [1 NTSC, 2 DVD] (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - 10. John Lilly's 78th Birthday Party [1 VHS] (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - 11. John Lilly Interview, Slick Productions, January 2000 [1 VHS, 2 DVD] (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - 12. John Lilly Interview Akaka TV Maui, 45 Minute Interview, June 1997 [1 VHS, 1 DVD] (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - 13. The Center of The Cyclone, John C. Lilly's 80th Birthday Party [2 VHS] (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - 14. Kindred Spirits, with John Lilly, a dolphin documentary [1 NTSC, 1 VHS] (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - 15. John C. Lilly Birthday 1996 [1 VHS] (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - 16. John Lilly In Tahiti Photo [1 VHS] (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - 17. Return Engagement, G.Gordon Liddy and Timothy Leary, brief appearance by John Lilly, and Arnold and Maria Schwarzenegger [1 VHS] (Box 140, Folder 9)
    - 18. The 5th International Dolphin and Whale Conference, Belgium 1996, with John C. Lilly [1 BCT Betacam] (Box 140, Folder 10)
    - 19. John Lilly in Europe in 1996, Touring Video [1 VHS] (Box 140, Folder 11)
    - 20. The Global Christmas. NHK TV with Timothy Leary and John C. Lilly [2 VHS] (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - 21. Mavericks of the Mind 2, Los Angeles, CA 1993 [1 VHS] (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - 22. October Gallery 1995 [2 PAL] (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - 23. John Lilly Birthday Videos, January 1996 [1 VHS] (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - 24. John Lilly 80th Birthday, Captured Video,1/6/1995 [3 VHS] (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - 25. Whale Adventures with John Lilly 1995 [1 VHS] (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - 26. Open Secret with John C. Lilly, May 2000 [1 VHS] (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - 27. John Lilly Audio "Aspen K" Talk 1974 [2 audiocassettes] (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - 28. John Lilly 1993 Maui Birthday [1 VHS] (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - 29. 24 High Resolution Scans of Lilly Photographs [1 CD-R] (Flat-box 142, Folder 1)
    - 30. John Lilly Interview in Basel 1998 [1 DVD] (Flat-box 142, Folder 2)